

DEEPTI KANDEL

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Vantaa, Finland

Deepti is an ambitious Software Developer with experience in creating both logical and complex web solutions in various programming languages. For example, while working at Bodhichitta Healthcare she designed a complete healthcare web app and showed equal potential when working at Shipit Oy Ab as a Junior Software Developer. Users at the interface have always been a subject of interest to her and she has shown a thorough and precise way of working on projects. Her previous projects show her ability to design thinking and knowledge of different technologies which makes her an excellent candidate for any Software company.

SKILLS

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT

Accessibility, Bootstrap, HTML, Figma, JavaScript, Material-UI, React.js, Alpine.js, Redux, SCSS, TypeScript, Livewire.

BACK-END DEVELOPMENT

Node.js, REST API, Php, Laravel.

DATABASE MANAGEMENT

MySQL, MongoDB.

DEVOPS

Bash, GitHub Actions, Netlify.

CLOUD SERVICES

LANGUAGES

English - Advanced

Finnish - Intermediate

Nepali - Native

RECENT PROJECTS

Countries API

Material UI, React.js, Redux, SCSS, Typescript.

An application built as part of Integrify's frontend project that fetches countries data from an API and displays in the interface. Includes features like search, sort, theme change, route to different page and add elements to cart and delete them.

Restaurant App

CSS, JavaScript, React.js.

A hobby project created to learn hooks from react. The app lets user to view restaurant menu and get description of the food items.

Portfolio App

Bootstrap, JavaScript, SCSS, React.js.

A portfolio website displaying services, skillset and contact information.

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Shipit Oy Ab | Lahti, Finland | September 2022 - December 2023

- Design, code, and support software solutions that can be easily scaled depending on the company needs.
- Maintain product quality by carrying out reviews, performing continual tests, analysing feedback, and managing software integration.
- Worked with different tech tools like: Php, Laravel, Livewire, Alpine.js, MySQL.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Integrify | Helsinki, Finland | April 2022 - September 2022

- Focusing on front-end development with JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Redux in addition to other technologies and concepts such as accessibility and animations.
- Building back-end for web-based applications with frameworks such as Node.js and Express.js.
- Covering additional concepts such as API development and documentation, unit testing with Jest, SQL and NoSQL databases, and version control with GitHub.
- Working with DevOps practices (Bash scripting, Docker containers, and CI/CD with GitHub Actions) and Cloud Services with AWS.

UX DESIGNER TRAINEE

Bodhichitta Healthcare | Chitwan, Nepal | March 2021 - October 2021

- Planned and conducted user research, workflow, and competitor analysis. Created user stories, personas, and storyboards as well as wireframes and functional prototypes.
- Received excellent feedback for my design thinking ability and knowledge of different tools used during the designing process such as Figma, Illustrator, and other business tools.

EDUCATION

BBA IN BUSINESS INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Haaga-Helia UAS | Helsinki, Finland | January 201? - December 2021